Gabriel Danaila

WEB DEVELOPER

gabriel.danaila.tech@gmail.com Tel: +1 615.825.0034 www.gabrieldanaila.com www.github.com/Gabriel-Danaila

WORK EXPERIENCE

iDesign - Netherlands

Feb 2021 - Present

Digital Agency

Web Developer - Freelancer

Proficient in using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Visual Studio Code, and Figma to craft responsive landing pages to meat client specifications, and testing the code across multiple platforms to ensure cross-browser compatibility and optimal functionality.

Managed version control with GitHub, collaborated with UX/UI designers to implement user-friendly interfaces and maintain a positive mindset with all team members.

Conducted routine code reviews and debugging sessions to improve website performance, optimize load times while consistently prioritising clean code practices.

Nissan - USA

Feb 2011 - Feb 2019

Battery Manufacturing Plant for Electric Vehicles

Maintenance Engineer Technician

I was responsible for maintaining automated equipment, using program backups, PLC diagnostic software, and perform calibration for cameras and sensors. Expertise in operating Omron Programmable Logic Controllers and managing Omron Vision System hardware and software

Proficiency in operating Mitsubishi and Yamaha industrial robots at the Nissan Battery Manufacturing Plant for Electric Vehicles

Leviton - USA

Feb 2010 - Feb 2011

Warehouse and Distribution Center Facilities

Maintenance Engineer Technician

I've actively engaged in the adoption of concepts such as Kaizen implementation, Root Cause Analysis for major Breakdown Reports, Corrective - Preventive - Predictive Maintenance, the 5S methodology designed to foster a quality work environment - Sort, Set in Order, Shine, Standardize, Sustain

Cinram - USA

Feb 2007 - Feb 2009

Warehouse and Distribution Center Facilities

Maintenance Engineer Technician

Architect of the Standard Operation Sheet Procedure (SOS), One Point Lessons for recurring tasks, standard steps, and resource identification for efficient task execution

HIGHLIGHTS

10 + years of experience I've effectively applying my extensive background in process engineering to web development. I've transitioned seamlessly from production lines to lines of code, and from intricate industrial robots to crafting modern, reliable websites and applications.

SKILLS

- HTML
- · CSS
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- React
- Node
- GitHub
- Figma
- · Visual Studio Code
- · Writing clean code
- · Problem solving

Work recognitions

- Battery Recognition Emblem Plate for Work Ethics - Nissan 2103
- Best Employee Recognition Award -Leviton 2012
- Perfect Attendance Award for Leviton 2011 / 2012

EDUCATION

Science Degree in Engineering (SIA) -Technology and Quality Control. University of Galati , 1998 – 2004

LANGUAGES

English – Fluent Romanian - Fluent